<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Venky&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://kovenky.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Venky&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2023, Venky.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 06:09:46 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kovenky.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Linear Regression : A Comprehensive Overview </title>
      <link>https://kovenky.github.io/2021/02/20/linear-regression-a-comprehensive-overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 06:09:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kovenky.github.io/2021/02/20/linear-regression-a-comprehensive-overview/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Linear regression is a basic machine learning algorithm used for supervised learning tasks involving prediction and forecasting. It is used to model the relationship between a dependent variable (target variable) and one or more independent variables (features/predictors) by fitting a linear equation to the observed data.
Sample Input The input to a linear regression model consists of:
A dataset with one or more independent variables (X) and a continuous target variable (y) The data is split into training and test sets The training data is used to train the model i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun Intro to K-NN Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://kovenky.github.io/2021/01/19/fun-intro-to-k-nn-algorithm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 06:09:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kovenky.github.io/2021/01/19/fun-intro-to-k-nn-algorithm/</guid>
      <description>Machine Learning Nuggets: A fun Introduction to K-NN Algorithm A girl from an orthodox family loved a boy while in college.
She informed her parents about this relation and expressed interest that she would like to marry him.
She shared all the details about the boy to her parents that she knew.
After some usual family drama, parents agreed to the wedding but with one condition that only if the boy passes background check.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
